Finding Aid for the Edward Huntsman-Trout Papers LSC.1186
UCLA Library Special Collections
Edward Huntsman-Trout papers
1916-1974
1923-1972
UCLA Library Special Collections
Huntsman-Trout, Edward
LSC.1186
20.5 Linear Feet (41 boxes)
101 oversize_boxes
Edward Huntsman-Trout (1889-1974) was a landscape architect. He worked in Boston and Ohio before starting a practice under his own name in Los Angeles. The collection consists primarily of blueprints and tissue designs as well as correspondence, sketches, and photographs related to Huntsman-Trout's work.
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of Mrs. Huntsman-Trout, 1977.
Gift of Neville and Mary Comerford, 1988.
Gift of Olivia Peter Huntsman-Trout, 1992.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9917205883606533
Biography
Edward Huntsman-Trout was born in Ontario, Canada, on July 31, 1889; graduated, University of California at Berkeley, 1913; attended Harvard School of Landscape Architecture, 1913-15; worked in the offices of Fletcher Steele, Boston, (1916), A.D. Taylor of Cleveland, Ohio (1917-22), and Rodeo Land and Water Company, Los Angeles, before engaging in practice under his own name; became a member of the American Society of Landscape Architects (ASLA), 1920; named an ASLA fellow, 1933; died, 1974.
Biographical Narrative
Edward Huntsman-Trout's career as a landscape architect spans the years 1932-1971. He was born in Ontario, Canada, on July 31, 1989, and following his graduation from the University of California in 1913, attended the Harvard University School of Landscape Architecture from 1913 to 1915. Before engaging in the practice of landscape architecture under his own name, he worked in the offices of Fletcher Steele, landscape architect, in Boston, 1916, and A.D. Taylor of cleveland, Ohio, 1917-22, and was employed as a landscape designer for Rodeo Land and Water Company, Los Angeles.
The collection of his papers consists, for the most part, of his tissue designs and blueprints for many prominent residences in the Souther California area, as well as a considerable body of institutional planning. Some of his more notable clients include Bing Crosby, Robert Young and Harvey Mudd, the last of whom retained him to work also on Scripps College in Claremont. Paul Trousdale, the noted Beverly Hills developer, employed him on his Trousdale Estates as well as on several other development projects, in both Los Angeles and the San Fernando Valley. His early work included the planning of actual structures with original designs for gates, lamps, fountains, etc., as well as their surrounding grounds, but as his career progressed, he confined himself almost entirely to landscape design.
Among his more notable institutional projects is the Los Angeles State and County Arboretum, located in Arcadia. Of special interest here is his work on the Hugo Reid Adobe House, first built in the mid-Nineteenth Century, and restored during the Arboretum Project amid some controversy as to its original structure. Other significant projects include Pershing Square and Lafayette Park.
There is little correspondence in the collection, and what there is deals almost exclusively with discussions between Huntsman-Trout and his clients on various aspects of the project in question.
Scope and Content
Collection consists primarily of blueprints and tissue designs from Edward Huntsman-Trout's career as a landscape architect in Southern California. There is extensive documentation of his work at Scripps College in Claremont and also at the Harvey Mudd residence in Benedict Canyon. Other projects in the collection include the Los Angeles County Arboretum, Los Angeles Turf Club, Pershing Square, Lafayette Park, and various residences in Beverly Hills and Los Angeles. The collection also includes correspondence, sketches, and photographs related to Huntsman-Trout's work.
Expanded Scope and Content
The collection consists of roughly 2000 architectural drawings, plans and blueprints dated 1922-1972, mostly stored folded in file folders which we have boxed by project number but with some rolled items. In addition, there is a very small amount of correspondence and 223 photographic prints and negatives. All the material relates to Huntsman-Trout's work as a landscape architect in the Los Angeles area and there is particularly full documentation of his work at Scripps College and the Harvey Mudd residence in Benedict Canyon during the 1930s.
Organization and Arrangement
Arranged in the following series:
Collection arranged alphabetically by client name.
Related Material
Edward Huntsman-Trout: Landscape Architect, by Lynn Marie Bryant. 1982. Library: SRLF Shelving number: D 000 731 115 2. vii. 98 leaves: ill. plans; 28 cm.
Charles Young Research Library, UCLA.
Sketches.; Blueprints.; Architectural drawings (visual works).; Photographs.; Huntsman-Trout, Edward, 1889-1974 --Archives.; Los Angeles State and County Arboretum; Los Angeles Turf Club; Scripps College.
- Client
  - Client: Alston., Garden., November 1944; 2 items. (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Client: Ambassador College, Pasadena., February 1951-November 1953.; 13 items. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Client: Ambassador Hotel, Los Angeles., October-December 1949.; 4 items. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Client: Anderson, H., Residence., February 1957; 4 items. (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Client: Anderson, L., Residence., January 1945-November 1946; 4 items. (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Client: Annandale Golf Club, Pasadena., March-August 1950.; 6 items. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Client: Araujo., Alterations., May 1949; 3 items. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Client: Ardrey., Residence., October 1951-January 1952; 5 items. (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Client: Arrowhead Springs Hotel, Arrowhead Hot Springs., June-November 1939.; 28 items. (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Client: Arrowhead Springs Hotel, Arrowhead Hot Springs., 3 items. (Box 135)
  - Client: Arrowhead Springs Hotel, Arrowhead Hot Springs. Photographs., 32 items. (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Client: Avon Products, Pasadena., November 1946-April 1947.; 3 items. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Client: Ayres, Jr., Residence., June 1936; 5 items. (Box 138)
  - Client: Ayres, Jr., Residence., March 1931-December 1940; 9 items. (Box 139)
  - Client: Ayres, Jr., Residence., March 1931-December 1940; 8 items. (Box 139)
  - Client: Ayres, Jr., Residence., February 1926-January 1931; 14 items. (Box 139)
  - Client: Ayres, Jr., Residence., March 1931-December 1940; 1 item. (Box 139)
  - Client: Ayres, Jr., Addition., February 1954; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Client: Ayres, Jr., Billing., June 1957; 4 items. (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Client: Ayres, Jr., House and garage specifications., March 1926; 9 items. (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Client: Ayres, Jr. Mounted small photographs., 3 items. (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Client: Backus, Jr., Residence., June 1952; 2 items. (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Client: Baldwin. Residence - photographs., 5 items. (Box 133)
  - Client: Baldwin., Residence., March 1923; 2 items. (Box 138)
  - Client: Baldwin., Mounted small photographs., February 1925; 6 items. (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Client: Baldwin Hills., 1 item. (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Client: Baldwin(?) see also: Rounds [identification unclear]. Photographs., 2 items. (Box 133)
  - Client: Ballif., Residence., July 1937; 2 items. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Client: Bard. (Box 129)
  - Client: Bard, Mrs. Richard., Correspondence, invoices., April 1970-February 1973; 41 item. (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Client: Bard, Richard., Residence., July 1951-March 1954; 15 items. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Client: Bard, Richard., Grounds., June 1962; 1 item. (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Client: Bard, Richard., Trellis., February 1966; 1 item. (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Client: Bard, Robert., Burial plot., November 1953-February 1957; 12 items. (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Client: Barker, Jr., Residence., April-May 1958; 3 items. (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Client: Baron., Grounds., September 1953-February 1954; 6 items. (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Client: Barrett., Accounts., May-June 1942; 7 items. (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Client: Bartlett., Grounds., April- July 1957; 4 items. (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Client: Bartlett., Additions., December 1968-May 1969; 9 items. (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Client: Bartlett, Hall., Correspondence, notes, invoices., August 1967-June 1973; 14 items. (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Client: Bauer., Residence., May-June 1955; 20 items. (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Client: Bauer., Grounds., March 1956; 7 items. (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Client: Bauersfeld., Estate., April 1943-December 1946; 9 items. (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Client: Bauman., Garden., June 1941; 2 items. (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Client: Baxter., Residence., August-September 1938; 4 items. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Client: Becker., Additions., October 1955; 7 items. (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Client: Bel-Air Hotel, Los Angeles., April-September 1961.; 2 items. (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Client: Belt., Residence., January 1934; 10 items. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Client: Belt. Residence., 3 items. (Box 77)
  - Client: Beverly Hills Nurseries., 8 items. (Box 77)
  - Client: Beverly-Arnaz Land Company, Beverlywood., July 1941.; 3 items. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Client: Bing., Grounds., February-May 1957; 6 items. (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Client: Bing., Correspondence., June-July 1957; 3 items. (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Client: Bishop., Residence., April-June 1958; 2 items. (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Client: Blanford., Grounds., May-July 1968; 22 items. (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Client: Bluhm., Residence., March-May 1937; 6 items. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Client: Blumstein., Grounds., May 1953; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Client: Bollenbacher., Garden., May 1949; 1 item. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Client: Bomber hide., November 1943.; 2 items. (Box 138)
  - Client: Bomber hide. Small photographs., 38 items. (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Client: Bomber hide. Photographs., 98 items. (Box 37, Folder 44)
  - Client: Bomber hide. (?)., 1943; 25 items. (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Client: Bomber hide. Drawing on board. (Box 98)
  - Client: Bomber hide(?). (?). Sketches., 1943; 17 items. (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Client: Booth., Residence., November 1937; 6 items. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Client: Boren., Grounds., December 1965-June 1968; 16 items. (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Client: Boston and Ohio(?). Photographs., 93 items. (Box 38, Folder 52)
  - Client: Boston, and, Ohio(?). Small mounted photographs., 15 items. (Box 38, Folder 55)
  - Client: Boxed tree, woman in foreground. Photographs., 2 items. (Box 38, Folder 46)
  - Client: Bracey., Residence., January 1940; 6 items. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Client: Brawerman., Residence., September 1967-April 1968; 7 items. (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Client: Bromsgrove Guild. Photographs, stained glass windows., 6 items. (Box 37, Folder 34)
  - Client: Bromsgrove Guild. Photographs, sconces, etc., 22 items. (Box 37, Folder 35)
  - Client: Bromsgrove Guild. Weathervanes, statuary., 60 items. (Box 37, Folder 36)
  - Client: Brown, F., Residence., June 1951; 2 items. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Client: Brown, F., Accounts., November 1951; 3 items. (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Client: Brown, G., Residence., February 1951-July 1952; 12 items. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Client: Brown, H., Residence., August 1951-May 1952; 3 items. (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Client: Brown, H., Additions., June-July 1955; 2 items. (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Client: Brown, H., Gates., February-April 1962; 6 items. (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Client: Brown, H. Residence., 4 items. (Box 56)
  - Client: Brown, W., Garden., June 1940; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Client: Brown, W. Garden., 6 items. (Box 47)
  - Client: Browne., Residence., April 1961-February 1965; 19 items. (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Client: Browne, Dr and Mrs Francis. (Box 92)
  - Client: Brunson., Residence., March 1952; 8 items. (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Client: Bullis., Residence., November 1934; 1 item. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Client: Burke., Residence., February 1933 (Box 127)
  - Client: Burke., Residence., February 1933 (Box 138)
  - Client: Caldwell., Grounds., October 1968-January 1969; 2 items. (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Client: Caldwell. Correspondence., 1 item. (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Client: California housing. Exhibit., 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Client: Camp Carmelita, Girl Scouts of America., Angeles Crest., April 1941; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Client: Carbon Mesa Road. Survey., 1 item. (Box __)
  - Client: Carmel. Mounted small photographs., 3 items. (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Client: Carnation Company Research Laboratory, Van Nuys., February 1953.; 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Client: Carnation Company Research Laboratory, Van Nuys., Court., June-September 1959; 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Client: Carnation Company Research Laboratory, Van Nuys(?). Photograph., 1 item. (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Client: Carnation Company, Los Angeles., May 1949.; 1 item. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Client: Carnation Company, Los Angeles., Additions., August 1954; 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Client: Chalet, entrance. Photographs., 3 items. (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Client: Chalet, in California mountains(?). Photographs., 2 items. (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Client: Chalet, landscaped., 1 item. (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Client: Chalet, portiere. Photographs., 3 items. (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Client: Chandler. Residence., 9 items. (Box 86)
  - Client: Chandler, Ralph J., Tissue drawings., August 1962-May 1966; 14 items. (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Client: Chandler, Ralph J., Invoice., June 1971; 1 item. (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Client: Chapman., Residence., April 1950; 1 item. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Client: Chappellet, C., Residence., February-June 1950; 9 items. (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Client: Chappellet, C., Additions., August-October 1952; 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Client: Chappellet, C., Improvements., March 1956-March 1959; 6 items. (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Client: Chappellet, C., Billing., October 1956; 2 items. (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Client: Chappellet, D., Grounds., March-June 1968; 5 items. (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Client: Chappellet, F., Residence., January-November 1937; 12 items. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Client: Chappellet, F., Residence., September 1936-December 1937; 32 items. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Client: Chi Omega Sorority House, UCLA., January-April 1957.; 3 items. (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Client: Chi Omega Sorority House, UCLA., 5 items. (Box 54)
  - Client: Citizens National Bank, Los Angeles., April-June 1948.; 1 item. (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Client: Clarke., Grounds., August 1952; 2 items. (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Client: Clements, Stiles O. Mounted small photographs., 3 items. (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Client: Cleveland filtration plant. Photographs of model., 2 items. (Box 37, Folder 39)
  - Client: Clum., Estate., July 1932-March 1934; 4 items. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Client: Cochran., Residence - 2 pcs. billing., May 1951; 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Client: Colborn., Residence., August 1929-January 1930; 2 items. (Box 138)
  - Client: Colman., Grounds., March-December 1956; 7 items. (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Client: Comerford, Neville. (Box 125)
  - Client: Comerford, Neville., Correspondence, invoices., June 1972-August 1973; 10 items. (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Client: Connery. Residence., 2 items. (Box 138)
  - Client: Convent. Photographs., 7 items. (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Client: Conway., Ranch., February 1935-August 1941; 5 items. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Client: Corby., Residence., March-July 1950; 5 items. (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Client: Cornell, Bridges & Troller., Carbon to Huntsman-Trout., January 14, 1957; 1 item. (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Client: Cornell, Ralph D., Letter., December 6, 1966; 1 item. (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Client: Cornell, Ralph D. Arboretum report, inscribed. (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Client: Cowen., Residence., November-December 1939; 7 items. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Client: Crawford Corporation, Baton Rouge., January-April 1954.; 5 items. (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Client: Crellin., Residence., August 1928; 1 item. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Client: Cromwell., Garden., June-October 1941; 4 items. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Client: Cunningham., Garden., February 1925; 3 items. (Box 138)
  - Client: Cunningham., Mounted small photographs., February 1925; 8 items. (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Client: Cunningham., Mounted small photograph., February 1925; 1 item. (Box 37, Folder 41)
  - Client: Curland., Residence., August-September 1936; 10 items. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Client: Dart., Residence., March-August 1962; 7 items. (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Client: Dart. Residence., 6 items. (Box 63)
  - Client: Davey., Garden., March 1939; 2 items. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Client: Davidson., Grounds., July 1952; 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Client: Day., Residence., March-June 1950; 3 items. (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Client: Day., Residence addition., July 1957; 1 item. (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Client: De Nubila., Garden., March 1958; 1 item. (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Client: Dentony., Grounds., February 1970; 15 items. (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Client: Desert. Mounted small photographs., 9 items. (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Client: Desert. Mounted small photographs., 2 items. (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Client: Desert. Mounted small photographs., 9 items. (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Client: Desert. Photograph., 1 item. (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - Client: Desert. Mounted small photographs., 7 items. (Box 37, Folder 42)
  - Client: Desert. Photograph., 1 item. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Client: Deutsch. Grounds., 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Client: Dietz., Additions., October 1961; 6 items. (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Client: Dietz., 5 items. (Box 67)
  - Client: Dixon., Residence., July-October 1948; 3 items. (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Client: Doheny. (Box 90)
  - Client: Don the Beachcomber, Los Angeles., Restaurant., January-April 1947; 3 items. (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Client: Downes. (Box 122)
  - Client: Dutcher., Garden., March 1948; 1 item. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Client: East Boston Park and Parkway System., Drawing (photograph)., 1915; 1 item. (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Client: Eckbo, Garrett. Correspondence, Huntsman-Trout. (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Client: Eckbo, Garrett., Correspondence, Huntsman-Trout., 1956-1957; 4 items. (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Client: Egyptian Theater, Hollywood. Mounted small photographs., 6 items. (Box 37, Folder 43)
  - Client: El Fureides. Mounted photograph., 1 item. (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - Client: English county services map., 1 item. (Box __)
  - Client: Etienne., Residence., March 1939-February 1940; 4 items. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Client: Exterior of house, garden. Photographs., 2 items. (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Client: Farmer., Residence., February 1954-February 1956; 14 items. (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Client: Faulkner., Residence., November 1948; 3 items. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Client: Fewel., Garden., November 1941; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Client: Field., Garden., December 1952-April 1953; 3 items. (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Client: Finch., Residence., October-November 1937; 5 items. (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Client: Fischmann. (Box 107)
  - Client: Fleishman., Residence., March-June 1956; 10 items. (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Client: Fluor., Residence., March-July 1948; 3 items. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Client: Forest Lawn Memorial Park, Glendale., May 1928.; 1 item. (Box 138)
  - Client: Forest scenes. Photographs., 2 items. (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Client: Frenke., Residence., October 1946-January 1947; 5 items. (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Client: Furstman., Residence., July-September 1946; 6 items. (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Client: Ganz, Jr., Residence., May 1961-August 1965; 5 items. (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Client: Garden. Photographs., 5 items. (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - Client: Gargiulo. Photographs., 2 items. (Box 38, Folder 42)
  - Client: Garrett., Residence., July-October 1933; 5 items. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Client: Gates (unidentified). Drawing. (Box 98)
  - Client: Gerry., Garden., April-October 1946; 7 items. (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Client: Gerry., Grounds., June 1952; 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Client: Gerry., Residence., October 1958-June 1959; 5 items. (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Client: Getting., Residence., November 1960; 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Client: Gilbert., Residence., December 1961-February 1962; 13 items. (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Client: Gillelen., Residence., February-March 1929; 4 items. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Client: Gilman. Stable., 1 item. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Client: Gilman., Accounts., April-May 1971; 7 items. (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Client: Given., Residence., May-September 1951; 6 items. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Client: Given., Additions., April-June 1953; 7 items. (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Client: Given Manufacturing Company, Vernon., December 1952-April 1953.; 3 items. (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Client: Good Housekeeping., Model house., August 1945; 2 items. (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Client: Grace, Charles. (Box 103)
  - Client: Grace, Charles., Correspondence, invoices., June 1971-June 1974; 90 items. (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Client: Graff., Grounds., May 1958-January 1959; 3 items. (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Client: Granada School, Los Angeles., February 1953.; 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Client: Grant, E., Residence., March-November 1926; 10 items. (Box 138)
  - Client: Grant, E., Residence., April-September 1926; 10 items. (Box 139)
  - Client: Grant, J., Residence., October 1956; 9 items. (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Client: Grant, J., Residence., July 1966; 1 item. (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Client: Greenfield. (Box 114)
  - Client: Greenfield., Pool., October 1961; 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Client: Greenfield., Repairs., March 1969; 1 item. (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Client: Gregg., Residence., January 1939; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Client: Gross, Susan Jane. The gardens of.....Huntsman-Trout. (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Client: Grossman., Grounds., November 1959-March 1960; 4 items. (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Client: Growell., Grounds., 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Client: Hall., Residence., June 1949-April 1950; 5 items. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Client: Halliburton., Residence., May 1955-September 1956; 7 items. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Client: Halliburton., Grounds., December 1962-November 1964; 6 items. (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Client: Hanson., Residence., n.d.; 3 items. (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Client: Hanson., Additions., April 1948-March 1950; 13 items. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Client: Hanson., Residence., April 1956-January 1957; 2 items. (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Client: Hardy, Jr., Residence., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Client: Hardy, Jr., Correspondence., September 1951; 1 item. (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Client: Hardy, R.H., Grounds., May-September 1957; 4 items. (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Client: Harnet. (Box 128)
  - Client: Harris, F., Pool., August 1945-September 1946; 6 items. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Client: Harris, H., Residence., July 1945; 4 items. (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Client: Harris, I., Residence., March-October 1948; 16 items. (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Client: Hart., Residence., n.d.; 2 items. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Client: Hawkes., Grounds., April 1934; 2 items. (Box 138)
  - Client: Hayden., Residence., March-May 1961; 7 items. (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Client: Hayden. Residence., 1 item. (Box 52)
  - Client: Hayward., Residence., September-October 1941; 3 items. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Client: Hayward., Residence., July 1945; 7 items. (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Client: Healey., Grounds., September-November 1953; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Client: Healey., Repairs., June-September 1955; 10 items. (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Client: Helms., Residence., 1935 September-February 1936; 4 items. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Client: Helms. Residence - Mott photographs., 10 items. (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Client: Helms. Residence - photographs., 3 items. (Box 132)
  - Client: Helms Bakeries, Los Angeles., January 1934.; 1 item. (Box 1, Folder 7)